Hello everyone!
This is Lithorlove!
Yay!
Please!
Today's project is Deden!
The 2nd Guguyo!
Congratulations!
Yay!
We did it!
This project is to see who knows the most about
This project is to decide who knows the most about Mr. Guguioru.
Hana-chan is strong, that's for sure.
Yes, but we can do it all with a project like this.
It's amazing!
It's difficult. It was difficult!
I tried to make it easy to understand.
I thought I made it easy to understand, but I thought you two might have twisted it a little too much. No, it's not! Not at all!
But it's okay when it's in your hands! I can handle it!
I know that part of you. I trust you.
I'll do my best!
Now, to the first question!
What made you happiest recently?
It's hard to be happy!
I can't play with people!
Ehhhhh!
Who did you tell that to?
I told Hitomi!
Ehhhh!
Let's go get Hitomi!
I want to call her!
I'm into this game lately!
I can't do it at home!
What kind of fun can't be had at home!
Aaaaah! It's getting harder and harder!
I went to play before Hana-chan's reading performance
I went to see her with it!
I think I know what it is!
Maybe this is a big clue!
Here it comes!
I think I just gave you a huge hint!
I don't know if I should be giving out so many hints.
Ha-ha-ha!
Okay, here we go!
OK!
Are you OK?
Let's all give our answers at once!
Ready!
Ta-da!
Oooooh!
Ha-ha-ha!
That's great!
Isn't it good?
I got a good one from UFO catcher!
I got a big stuffed animal at UFO catcher!
Woooo!
It's so similar!
Almost the same!
What do you think? Did you get it?
I'm curious!
Let's see the answers!
What do you think?
I got a stuffed animal from UFO Catcher in one shot.
Ohhh!
What should I do with it?
What was the stuffed animal like? Big?
You know, a series of stuffed animals in the size of a nyan cat that Hitomi likes.
I got this brand of stuffed animal, and I called Hitomi, so that means she knows about it.
It was a one-shot deal, that's why I was so happy.
0.5!
I almost hit it!
Don't you want 0.8?
But I think I can do it.
Okay!
Question number two!
What's the most embarrassing story you've heard recently?
Embarrassing story?
I don't know.
Do we know?
I don't think so!
It's not so much embarrassing as it is a little awkward.
It's more like, "Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I think some people do it sometimes.
Maybe I've done it once or twice.
I feel like I want to tell you everything.
Just keep saying it.
Can you just keep saying it?
Lower half!
Lower half!Lower half?
Lower half?
Lower half! Lower body!
Somewhere in the lower half.
Oh, you got it?
That's great.
Did you get it?
Okay. - Okay.
Here we go.
Ready!
Two!
The shoe book was open.
I went out with a shoe board in a different pattern.
Yeah, that's possible.
Which one is it?
Oh, my God, that's nice!
Is it nice?
It's nice!
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
It's coming out, isn't it?
It's alive, right? It's alive, isn't it?
I think it's good.
But I think this is possible, too.
You do that a lot, don't you?
I'm doing it, right?
Yes, I do.
I don't know. It's like an image.
Oh, yeah, this could be it.
Let's see it! Let's see it!
At the fitting.
When I looked at the back of the socks
I looked at the back of the sock and was told it was the other way around.
I was like, "Hee-hee!
What?
That's too close!
Nice try!
But it's kind of right, isn't it?
Socks. Socks point.
Sock point.
No!
0.5
0.5!
But 1 point.
One point! Yay!
But I'm wearing a shoe book.
To Chiara
The other day, Yori-chan
I remembered that Yori-chan pointed out to me
I remembered that Yori pointed out that my shoe book was open again.
I did! I was doing this too!
I was doing this too!
0.5
0.2
0.2!
0.4!
Thank God! I got it!
I got it! I got it!
You're doing better than I thought you would.
It's good. It's good.
Here we go! Question 3.
What's the first song you want to sing at karaoke?
What's that?
Oh, I don't know.
This is really hard.
I want to sing the song I really sing.
A song you're really singing.
What do you mean?
Like a real song.
Like singing?
Love? Love songs?
Love songs!
Wait, wait, wait. I don't know.
I don't know. If there's any words.
I'll get like 0.1 points or something.
Oh, man, they think I'm so easy.
Here we go!
Ready!
Here we go.
Aah!
A Love Story
Inside Birth
Intra-natal
You've made it.
That's your kind of taste? Sort of
Wajirabu 100%.
What? It's there, isn't it? This song
It's WAJIRABU 1000%, isn't it?
Aaah! I made a mistake!
Aaah! Too close!Ah! Almost!
I made a mistake.
I had heard that this song is very exciting.
I heard that in an interview or something.
That's true, isn't it?
I'm sure you'll sing your favorite song.
Let's see if you can answer!
DODON DODON DODON!
Today...
Today?
Let's see...
The back down.
Aah!
Is that the flower?
Aaaaah!
Which one was it?
You're Mr. Bucknumber. I'm the official beard guy.
Wait a minute. I couldn't get it out of my head.
Oh, you got lost today?
Lost?
Yeah, I was torn between the bearded guy and the back number guy.
How are you feeling today?
Mr. Back Number, huh?
Wow, I'd love to hear that. That's a good choice.
Zero.
Zero, I guess.
I think we're going to have to give up.
Question number four. Don!
If you could take one member on a desert island survival trip, who would it be?
This one's got no twist at all.
Everybody face the camera here.
I mean, there's only one other person.
This one, I want you to guess.
Okay.
Here you go, chocolate.
Oh!
Survivalist, aren't you?
Yeah, you're right. You do talk a good game.
He caught a fish with his bare hands.
And he cooked the fish he just took.
He cooked it for me.
I know, I know.
If it's chocolate...
Let's hope. Let's see what the answer is. Go ahead.
Would you prefer a practical or a healing member?
I see.
Takewaki!
Yay!
Shaka, right?
I like Shaka.
She makes me feel safe.
Score one.
One point.
That's good.
By the way, who would you take with you if you were a member of the healing group?
Risa Kamianyan
Annya
Toys
I'll be with you then, too.
Heavy.
heavy
This is the fifth question. What is your favorite part?
Wait, that's so hard.
I've been trying to say this to my fans lately when they ask me what I like about myself.
Words.
I'm glad people are thinking about it.
I'll keep it simple and just say what I think.
So, should I say that's my favorite part for both of you?
Wait a minute. It's not the same.
It's not?
Let's go. Let's go.
He says it's a popular place.
You've been saying that a lot lately, but I don't think it's right.
I think it's the gap.
Everyone thinks this, so I wondered what it is.
Then let's see the correct answer.
Sensitivity?
Suddenly you are answering seriously.
The correct answer is that I am sensitive.
No doubt.
But, Incho, you are right.
I'm sure you are.
I am happy.
I think that's probably the thing that makes me happiest when people say that to me.
I'm sure he's very happy when he hears it from Sajihara-san, too.
And the gap.
I think it's one of my charms.I think it's part of my charm.
I'm glad.
You understand yourself.
I'm happy, happy, happy. Finally.
I can cry.
I can cry, really.
But zero points.
Zero points.
Next is the sixth question.
What is your most unforgettable memory of the collaboration?
I think you know what I mean.
I've said it a lot. In many places.
There are so many, which is the best?
I can't decide.
I know.
For public appearances.
I know what you mean. I don't think so.
When did you start?
At the beginning.
What?
Huh?
Hey.
I got it.
Inkyou first.
Yes.
It went.
I'm sure I overdid it.
Here you go.
Ready.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
We all sang together during the shooting of the music video.
I remember.
It's good, isn't it?
It brings back memories.
I miss it.
I'm full of it.
The very first Fulfull.
We sang, and after the press conference, we all thanked each other for our hard work,
When we broke up, we said let's exchange contact information,
It was fullfull, wasn't it?
It was full, full, full.
It brings back memories.
That's it.
It was the first time for both of us, wasn't it?
First.
Let's look at the correct answer.
In between the shooting of the music video for the first single,
We all sang while doing small fry.
This is it.
It was very memorable.
Ana, you got it right!
You got it right.
We did it! We did it!
That's great.
You even got it right on this one.
It's one of my favorite memories.
That's great. When I think about it, you're right.
It makes me feel warm and fuzzy.
One point.
I hope I win. 1 point.
Yay!
This is the second question.
I'll do my best. Let's go for it.
Here is the seventh question.
What is Emily Otani's second favorite part?
Second favorite part?
The first thing?
She has two firsts.
It's so simple.
Simple?
Do I even know what I'm talking about?
I do!
Because I do!
Simple!
Simple?
Simple and clear!
Everyone loves it!
I see. There.
There are so many meanings.
This guy is amazing.
I guess that's what it means.
What's your favorite part?
This one.
Which is your second favorite part?
This way?
Let's keep it simple.I'll keep it simple.
Simple.
Simple!
Really simple.
Really. Here we go.
Ready!
Aaaaah!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. Face? Face! Yes, it's great.
She's so cute. Yes, wonderful.
Excellent! They're both right, right?
Let's see what's right.
I'm torn.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's so cute!
So cute!
Wow!
You're right, it's cute.
I went a little overboard.
I think Miri gets one this time.
Yay!
So...
How many points?
2.3
2.7
Three.
Last question?
Last question
LAST QUESTION
If you were to go on a date with Hana, where would you most like to go?
I think you have the advantage here, Hana-chan.
I'm not sure.
I want to go there and Hana-chan said she wants to go there too.
I see.
That's what she said.
She did.
There's so many of them.
There's a lot of them.
Lots of them.
Yes, sir.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
Zoo.
Uh...
Sleepy Hut
Sleepy Houses
Sleepy Hollow
I've done the aquarium and the aquarium, but I've always said it's an animal park.
Uh...
There's a lot of animals.
Yeah, there's a lot of animals.
Sleepyheads.
I have a lot of flowers.
You have so many!
So many.
So I thought maybe that's it.
And the two of us go out a lot under her.
We go to see flowers.
That's for sure.
Let's see the correct answers.
There are three places Hana-chan and I have said we want to go.
Three.
The first of them is the Animal Park.
Ah!
Yay!
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
That was great.
It was an animal park.
Happy zoo!
Yay!
That's amazing... how well you two remember everything.
I keep saying it.
You've been saying it.
I'm not saying it now.
I'm not saying it.
Final results, then.
Yes, sir.
The mini-shop.
Three.
I got 3.7.
By 0.7
I got Noguo!
That's amazing!
That's great!
Yay!
That was indeed a big leaf flower!
Thank you so much!
That's amazing.
It's only 0.7, though.0.7, though.
I'm glad you got it right.
Oh, good.
I'm glad.
I'm so happy.
Okay, bye-bye, everybody.
Bye, bye, bye.
Suki-suki, everybody!
I love you!
I love
Suki Suki
Suki Suki.
Good, good, good.
I'm glad.
Bye bye bye.